#### **DEIVID DE MATTOS SILVA**

Brazilian, Stamp4 Dublin, Swords Skype- deivid132

Contact: +353 0899429264 deividmattos79@hotmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/deivid

# **RESUME**

I've been a Web Designer for 4 years, I am passionate about the Web environment, especially HTML5, CSS3,PHP, Wordpress and responsive design. I am self-motivated to challenge myself with new layouts, and discover new things. I always look forward to meeting new people, collaborating with the staff, sharing my knowledge, attaining new skills, and improving them. I am also very enthusiastic about Web development. I've been working with JavaScript and jQuery for about 2 years, and I like how React get things done. I am a very proactive, open-minded and easy-going person, and I am always keen on learning more.

# TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

My main skills are HTML5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, designing HTML for email clients, and also converting PSD's layout into a functional online prototype. there's a list of my technical skills Below:

- HTML 5
- CSS3
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- React
- Wordpress
- GitHub

# **Courses**

- SAP Academy Material Management (MM Material Master and SD Sales and Distribution), Ka Solution
- Functional SAP R/3 Foundation and SAP ABAP Academy, Training Education Services.
- Mainframe to Cobol, GPTI Training
- Programming Logic Impacta

### **EDUCATION**

Municipal <u>University</u> of São Caetano do sul São Paulo - Brazil

January 2011 – December. 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Uninove University - São Paulo Brazil

January 2019 - December 2019

Postgraduate in Systems and Web Development.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

• Tgestiona Logística - Brazil

April 2019 - October 2021

Software Developer - Working with developing software for company. Always working with new technologies such as HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress, React, MVC, Git.

Development of Web pages and special development of internal transport systems.

#### • 4WSITES Ltda - Brazil

July.2018 - December 2018

Software Developer - Working with, developing websites for stores. Always working with new technologies such as HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, PHP, Wordpress, etc. Development of Websites and Web apps with up to date web standards.

### • Fix2u Technical Assistance Ltda - Brazil

**September 2016 - May 2018** 

Junior Front-End Programmer - Working with, developing software for stores. Always working with new technologies such as HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, Javascript . Development of Web pages and special campaigns for a travel agency company.

• Magna Sistema Consultoria Ltda. – Brazil

January 2016 - July 2016

Solutions Analyst EAM Junior I - Service provision, internal service. I worked with clients such as Concremat, Serpro, and Neo Energia.

• Stefanini Consultoria e Assessoria - Brazil

September 2014 – December 2015

(Medium-sized company in the IT consulting services segment) Position: SAP Functional Analyst-Provision of services for the company Nestlé S/A. Supporting SAP modules MM and SD users. Document processing (orders, deliveries and requests /IDocs); Inclusion and verification of customers in the SAP system, via workflow; Extraction of monthly reports of materials, suppliers and WBS elements; Maintenance and records of entries in the SAP system, as well as, blocks and extensions of materials for other existing centers and warehouses; Changes and revisions from customers and suppliers.